[
  {
    "Front": "ὑβρίζω",
    "Back": " vb.: øver vold"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὕβρις",
    "Back": " sb. 3 f.: vold"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑβριστής",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: voldsmand"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑγιαίνω",
    "Back": " vb.: er rask"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑγίεια",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: sundhed"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑγρός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: våd"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὕδωρ",
    "Back": " sb. 3 n.: vand"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑιός",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: søn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὕλη",
    "Back": " sb. 1 f.: materiale, brænde"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑµεῖς",
    "Back": " pron.: I"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπέρ",
    "Back": " præp. m. akk.: op over"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπέρ",
    "Back": " præp. m. gen.: oven over"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπηρετέω",
    "Back": " vb.: tjener"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπηρέτης",
    "Back": " sb. 1 m.: tjener"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπισχνέοµαι",
    "Back": " vb.: lover"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὕπνος",
    "Back": " sb. 2 m.: søvn"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπό",
    "Back": " præp. m. gen.: under; af [agens]"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπό",
    "Back": " præp. m. akk.: ind under"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑπό",
    "Back": " præp. m. dat.: nedenfor"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὕστερος",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: senere"
  },
  {
    "Front": "ὑψηλός",
    "Back": " adj. 1-2: højre"
  }
]